Contact

lindseyfarley@outlook.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lindsey-farley-8770b8172 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Operating Room

Medical Intensive Care

Pediatric Intensive Care

Certifications
CCRN

Lindsey Farley

Registered Nurse at CHI St. Luke's Health

Houston, Texas Area

Summary

I am a healthcare entrepreneur with almost ten years of experience as a registered nurse. My mission is to empower women to become the very best versions of themselves through hard work and personal development.

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing, Customer Service, Microsoft Word, Medical-Surgical, and Medical Intensive Care. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science - BS focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from University of Oklahoma Health Sciences Center.

Experience

CHI St. Luke's Health
Registered Nurse
January 2018 - Present (2 years 5 months)

Memorial Hermann Health System Registered Nurse April 2014 - January 2018 (3 years 10 months) Houston, Texas Area

Pediatric ICU nurse

OU Medicine, Inc.
Registered Nurse
June 2009 - March 2014 (4 years 10 months)
Oklahoma City, Oklahoma Area
pediatric OR circulator until February 2013

pediatric Ort circulator until 1 cordary 2010

Adult medical/surgical ICU February 2013- March 2014

Page 1 of 2

Education

University of Oklahoma Health Sciences Center Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2004 - 2009)